Unitex 3.1beta - Copyright (C) 2001-2014
Université Paris-Est Marne-la-Vallée <unitex@univ-mlv.fr>
Web site: http://www-igm.univ-mlv.fr/~unitex/
Mailing list: unitex-users@univ-mlv.fr

Unitex is a linguistic software engine. This software uses the Unicode 3.0 standard for character encoding.

Unitex is a free software. It's own code is LGPL-licensed.
Some functionalities of Unitex are based on the 
TRE library version 0.8.0, which is BSD-licensed. The author of the TRE library is Ville Laurikari (vl@iki.fi). 
The web site of this library are http://laurikari.net/tre/ and https://github.com/laurikari/tre/
TRE is released under a license which is essentially the same as the “2 clause” BSD-style license used in NetBSD.
See the file LICENSE, included in the source code package tre-0.8.0.tar.gz, for details.

Unitex uses LibYAML. The LibYAML library is written by Kirill Simonov.
LibYAML is released under the MIT license (see MIT_libyaml.txt and LICENCE in yaml-0.1.6.tar.gz).
LibYAML website are http://pyyaml.org/wiki/LibYAML and https://bitbucket.org/xi/libyaml

Unitex includes LORIA's LGPL alignment program XAlign (http://led.loria.fr/outils/ALIGN/align.html).

This product includes software developed by the Apache Software Foundation (http://www.apache.org/). xercesImpl.jar and xmlParserAPIs.jar, used by Xalign, are Apache-2.0-licensed.

getopt for Windows:
This product includes software developed by the NetBSD Foundation, Inc. and its contributors.
This product includes software developed by the University of California, Berkeley and its contributors.

You can redistribute Unitex and the libraries and programs it contains and/or modify them under the terms of their respective licenses.

The dictionaries that are included in Unitex are LGPLLR-licensed.
